+359885452670IVAN.V.DIMITROV@PM.ME LINKEDIN.COM/IN/VANJIII GITHUB.COM/VANJIII

Ivan Dimitrov

ABOUT

I am a backend software engineer who is a fast learner, enjoys challenges and enjoys working in a high energy environment using modern technologies. I am used to applying agile methodologies and breaking down user requirements. I am not afraid of making decisions and taking responsibility. I have also experience with enterprise projects using Java and Android.

Professional EXPERIENCE

StageAI, Sofia

Senior Software Developer

May 2020 - Present

- ▶ Solve complex tasks mainly using GOlang and PostgreSQL;
- ▶ Provide and help others to provide clean and efficient code;
- ▷ Supervise the working processes applying agile methodologies;
- ▶ Breakdown tasks and requirements.

Software Developer

Jan 2018 - May 2020

- ▷ Develop various web application using mainly with GOlang, SQL, REST and Graphql;
- ▷ Deliver high quality code;
- ▶ Follow best practices like TDD, refactoring and code standards.

Musala Soft, Sofia

Software developer

Aug 2016 - Dec 2017

> Worked as a contractor for Experian maintaining their existing project using mainly internal tools in the Java ecosystem.

Junoir Software Developer

Aug 2015 - Aug 2016

- ▶ Developed native android applications with Java;
- ▶ Maintained Java Enterprise application using JSP, maven, OracleDB;
- ▶ Maintained hybrid mobile application with Javascript and apache Cordova.

Game developer-intern, Varna

Software Developer

Aug 2014 – Sept 2014

SKILLS

Golang, PostgreSQL, GraphQL, RESTFul services, GIT.

EDUCATION

Technical University, Varna

M.S. of Computer Science Sep 2013 - June 2015 B.S. of Electronics Sep 2009 - June 2013

CERTIFICATIONS Oracle Certified Professional, Oracle

Sep 2017

Agile Software Development, The Business Institute

Apr 2017

Managing Team Performance, The Business Institute

Feb 2017

Oracle Certified Associate, Oracle

Nov 2016